# BYEONGJOO AHN

Porter Hall B5, 5000 Forbes Ave, Pittsburgh, PA 15213

Homepage: https://byeongjooahn.com & Email: bahn@cmu.edu

### RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interests are in computational imaging and computer vision. I am interested in identifying visible hints offered by our physical surroundings such as interreflections, and developing imaging systems extending the visibility far beyond human ability such as the reconstruction of objects that are not in the direct line of sight or those with strong self-occlusions.

#### **EDUCATION**

Carnegie Mellon University

Ph.D. Candidate in Electrical and Computer Engineering Sep. 2017 – Present

Advisors: Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan and Ioannis Gkioulekas

**Seoul National University** 

Seoul, Korea Mar. 2012 - Feb. 2014

M.S. in Electrical Engineering and Computer Science

Advisor: Kyoung Mu Lee

Thesis: "Occlusion-Aware Motion Deblurring for Bilayer Scenes"

Outstanding Thesis Award

**Seoul National University** 

Seoul, Korea Mar. 2008 - Feb. 2012

B.S. in Electrical and Computer Engineering Summa Cum Laude

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Carnegie Mellon University

Research Assistant

Pittsburgh, PA Sep. 2017 – Present

Pittsburgh, PA

- · Developed a full surround 3D imaging system that we call kaleidoscopic structured light, comprising a projector, a camera, and a kaleidoscope
- · Developed an imaging method to reconstruct hidden 3D shapes from multiply scattered photon using time-of-flight (ToF) information at picosecond timescale resolution (a.k.a. Non-Line-of-Sight Imaging)

Snap Inc. (Remote) New York, NY

Research Intern with Jian Wang and Shree Nayar, Computational Imaging Group

May. 2020 - Aug. 2020

· Worked on improving Snapcode/QR code detection by increasing the maximum scanning distance

### Korea Institute of Science and Technology

Seoul, Korea

Research Scientist, Center for Imaging Media Research

Mar. 2014 - Aug. 2017

- · Developed multiple-camera capture system with 3D multi-view deblurring algorithm for dynamic 3D facial reconstruction
- · Developed polarized lighting system with an algorithm for real time acquisition of specular and diffuse normal maps from minimal number of polarized images
- · Developed web application for Korean food classification using Caffe and Flask web server

**HP Labs** Palo Alto, CA

Research Intern with Irwin Sobel

Jan. 2012 - Feb. 2012

· Developed 3D video mobile controller using PTZ robot and Android phone

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

### "Kaleidoscopic Structured Light"

**Byeongjoo Ahn**, Ioannis Gkioulekas, Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan *ACM Transactions on Graphics (Proc. SIGGRAPH ASIA)*, 2021

# "Convolutional Approximations to the General Non-Line-of-Sight Imaging Operator"

**Byeongjoo Ahn**, Akshat Dave, Ashok Veeraraghavan, Ioannis Gkioulekas, Aswin C. Sankaranarayanan *IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV)*, 2019 (Oral Presentation)

# "Occlusion-Aware Video Deblurring with a New Layered Blur Model"

**Byeongjoo Ahn**, Tae Hyun Kim, Wonsik Kim, Kyoung Mu Lee *arXiv preprint arXiv:1611.09572*, 2016

# "Reduced Illumination Patterns for Acquisition of Specular and Diffuse Normal Maps"

Byeongjoo Ahn, Junghyun Cho, Taekyung Yoo, Ig-Jae Kim

ACM SIGGRAPH ASIA Poster, 2016

## "Dynamic Scene Deblurring"

Tae Hyun Kim, Byeongjoo Ahn, Kyoung Mu Lee

IEEE International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2013

#### AWARDS AND HONORS

| Doctoral Study Abroad Scholarship, Korea Foundation for Advanced Studies | 2017 |
|--------------------------------------------------------------------------|------|
| Fulbright Graduate Study Award (Declined), Fulbright                     | 2017 |
| Best Poster Award, KIST R&D EXPO                                         | 2014 |
| Outstanding Thesis Award, Department of EECS, Seoul National University  | 2014 |
| Honorable Mention Award, Samsung Humantech Paper Award                   | 2014 |
| Graduate Scholarship, Kwanjeong Educational Foundation                   | 2012 |
| Presidential Science Scholarship, Korea Student Aid Foundation           | 2008 |

### **TEACHING**

Teaching Assistant, Carnegie Mellon University

- · 15-463/663/862 Computational Photography
- · Recitation for 18-290 Signals and Systems

Fall 2020

Spring 2019, 2020

# **SERVICES**

Reviewer, CVPR 2019-2021; ICCV 2019-2021; ECCV 2020; BMVC 2019

Volunteer, Camera Building Workshop as part of Gelfand Outreach Program at CMU (2019)

Student Volunteer, ACCV 2012; ICCP 2021

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Proficient with MATLAB, Python, C/C++; Conversant with C#, JavaScript

#### **GRADUATE COURSEWORK** 15-868 Physics-based Rendering Spring 2021 33-353 **Intermediate Optics** Fall 2020 15-858 Discrete Differential Geometry Spring 2020 18-771 Linear Systems Fall 2019 10-707 Deep Learning Spring 2019 Convex Optimization 10-725 Fall 2018 16-823 Physics based Methods in Vision Spring 2018 Introduction to Machine Learning 10-701 Spring 2018 16-720B Computer Vision Fall 2017 18-793 Image and Video Processing Fall 2017 **Intermediate Statistics** 36-705 Fall 2017

Last updated: Sep 14, 2021